At a time when the Democratic Party is losing some support among Latinos, among black voters,
Nikki Haley, who, like you, is of Southeast Asian descent,
said this week that this country has never been a racist country.
So let me ask you directly.
Do you agree that America has never been a racist country?
You know, I, first of all, and I think everyone agrees, we all agree,
the issue of race in America is not something that should be the subject of a soundbite.
Right.
The history of racism in America should never be the subject of a soundbite
or a question that is meant to elicit a one-sentence answer.
But there is no denying that we have in our history as a nation
racism and that racism has played a role in the history of our nation.
And when I think about it, I think we all would agree that while it is part of our past
and we see vestiges of it today, we should also be committed collectively
to not letting it define the future of our country.
But we cannot get to a place of progress on the issue of race
by denying the existence of racism.
By denying...
...